<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Strike Debt!</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Debt Resistance for the 99%</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 01:15:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.0.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Is Strike Debt still active?</title>
		<link>/is-strike-debt-still-active/</link>
		<comments>/is-strike-debt-still-active/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 23:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel Hong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1666</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Strike Debt is a decentralized network of debt resisters, including activists, artists, and organizers. Started in New York City in 2012, Strike Debt has achieved much since its origin: the creation of anti-debt organizations around the US, the writing and publication of The Debt Resisters’ Operations Manual, and the material support and organizational base for &#8230;]]></description>
		<wfw:commentRss>/is-strike-debt-still-active/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>All Our Grievances Are Connected</title>
		<link>/all-our-grievances-are-connected/</link>
		<comments>/all-our-grievances-are-connected/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 17:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jacques]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1602</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In the United States we are finally witnessing a steadily increasing backlash against police militarization, murder at the hands of police and the general devaluation of Black life. At the same time, there is a growing movement against debt in our society: the fact that in order to survive — to get ourselves basic needs like food, shelter, healthcare and education — we are forced to go into debt. It may not be apparent on first glance, but there are deep connections between these struggles.]]></description>
		<wfw:commentRss>/all-our-grievances-are-connected/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Department of Education Announces Sale of 56 Corinthian Campuses, Solidifies Its Support of Criminal For-Profit Colleges Instead of Defrauded Students</title>
		<link>/corinthiansale/</link>
		<comments>/corinthiansale/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 21:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1593</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Department of Education should be a responsible steward of the nation’s colleges and universities. These days it’s acting more like a debt collector for a predatory lender. Today’s announcement of the sale of 56 Corinthian College campuses to Education Credit Management Corporation really drives this fact home. As former Everest student Geovanna Nieves noted, &#8230;]]></description>
		<wfw:commentRss>/corinthiansale/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rolling Jubilee Student Debt Buy</title>
		<link>/debtbuy4/</link>
		<comments>/debtbuy4/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 22:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1542</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Strike Debt’s Rolling Jubilee project has abolished almost $4 million in private student debt for a little over $100,000 These debts were held by students who attended Everest College, a predatory for-profit institution in the Corinthian Colleges network. You can read a sample letter received by debtors here. Details about the purchase are available here. &#8230;]]></description>
		<wfw:commentRss>/debtbuy4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coming on September 17 – Rolling Jubilee Debt Buy #4</title>
		<link>/update4/</link>
		<comments>/update4/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 12:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1535</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This time, it’s different. Since the beginning of the Rolling Jubilee campaign, we&#8217;ve wanted to buy and abolish student debt. But most student loans are guaranteed by the federal government, and so they are not available for purchase. As part of our effort to buy private, unsecured student loans, we talked to Doug St. Peters, &#8230;]]></description>
		<wfw:commentRss>/update4/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reportback from the First Debtors’ Assembly at Southern Illinois University</title>
		<link>/carbondalereport/</link>
		<comments>/carbondalereport/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 14:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Events]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1511</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[By Strike Debt Carbondale Reposted from Midwest Campus Crisis We held a Debtors’ Assembly on April 10 outside of the Student Center on Southern Illinois University campus. Inspired by Strike Debt, an offshoot of Occupy Wall Street, our only plan for the assembly was to come with some personal stories about how debt affects our &#8230;]]></description>
		<wfw:commentRss>/carbondalereport/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cloudy with a Chance of Radicalism: How Broken Chain of Title Can Turn the Tables on Banks</title>
		<link>/cloudy-with-a-chance-of-radicalism/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 22:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mike Andrews]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=982</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In an earlier post on this website, we told the story of Richmond, California, a small city with big plans to end its foreclosure crisis via a novel use of eminent domain. If successful, this plan could set a nationwide precedent, and Strike Debt Bay Area (@StrikedebtBA), among other groups, is fighting to push it &#8230;]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nine Arguments For Debt Refusal</title>
		<link>/nine-arguments/</link>
		<comments>/nine-arguments/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 15:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=877</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[By Andrew Ross Every other day brings us fresh headlines about malfeasance, fraud and continued predatory behavior on the part of the finance industry. Morally speaking, bankers are the most depraved and derelict actors in our society. And yet they continue to rely upon heavy-duty moralism to enforce debtors’ obligations. What is an appropriate response? &#8230;]]></description>
		<wfw:commentRss>/nine-arguments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Commonly asked questions: Aren&#8217;t the debts you buy &#8220;worthless,&#8221; or &#8220;uncollectable&#8221;?</title>
		<link>/caq-worthless/</link>
		<comments>/caq-worthless/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 17:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[aaronb]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Commonly Asked Questions]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=759</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[[We get a lot of questions by email, and we do our best to respond to each and every one personally. Though we have a short FAQ on the Rolling Jubilee website, many questions deserve more in-depth responses. We&#8217;ve decided to post longer answers to some of the more common questions on this blog, in &#8230;]]></description>
		<wfw:commentRss>/caq-worthless/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reflections on the History of Debt Resistance: The Case of El Barzón</title>
		<link>/elbarzon/</link>
		<comments>/elbarzon/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 15:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=696</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[By George Caffentzis Originally published in the dossier, Against the Day, in the fall 2013 issue of South Atlantic Quarterly Introduction As part of my work with Strike Debt, I have been reexamining the history of debt resistance in order to place our organization in a historic perspective. Elsewhere, I have studied ancient, medieval, and &#8230;]]></description>
		<wfw:commentRss>/elbarzon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
